Gary Fisher Papers, 1973-1997 GLC 51
James C. Hormel Gay & Lesbian Center, San Francisco Public Library
- Correspondence, 1982-1994; Series 5; 4.0 folders + 1 oversized folder
  - Between Gary Fisher and Eve Sedgwick, 1987-1994, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Includes: hospital poems, May 1993; notes, undated; memorial leaflet for Fisher, 1994.
  - Karen Kelly, Dia Center for the Arts, to Eve Sedgwick, regarding Sedgwick's participation in the conference "Constructing Masculinity,", April 1994 (Box 3, Folder 48, Oversize-folder 2)
    Includes: program booklet, poster, Sedgwick's talk "Gosh, Boy George You Must Be Awfully Secure in Your Masculinity!", and a 3-1/2-inch computer disk.
  - Donna Ward-Kiddo to Eve Sedgwick, enclosing photocopies of letters from Fisher, 1982-1994 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Printed Materials, 1995; Series 6; 1.0 folder
  The series contains one periodical issue in which Fisher's "Red Cream Soda" is published.
  - Evergreen Chronicles, Summer/Fall 1995 (Box 3, Folder 50)